[
  {
    "question": "What is ReactJS??",
    "answers": [
      "Server-side Framework",
      "User-interface framework",
      "Both",
      "None"
    ],
    "answerSelectionType": "single",
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Everything in React is a?",
    "answers": [
      "Module",
      "Component",
      "Package",
      "Class"
    ],
    "answerSelectionType": "single",
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Babel?",
    "answers": [
      " A transpiler.",
      "An interpreter",
      "A Compiler",
      "Both Compiler and Transpilar"
    ],
    "answerSelectionType": "single",
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "How many elements does a react component return",
    "answers": [
      "2 Elements",
      "1 Element",
      "Multiple Elements"
    ],
    "answerSelectionType": "single",
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How can you access the state of a component from inside of a member function?",
    "answers": [
      "this.getState()",
      "this.prototype.stateValue",
      "this.state",
      "this.values"
    ],
    "answerSelectionType": "single",
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "JavaScript can be used in ____ development",
    "answers": [
      "Back-End",
      "Front-End",
      "ReactJS",
      "All of the Above"
    ],
    "answerSelectionType": "single",
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Props are __________ into other components",
    "answers": [
      "Injected",
      "Methods",
      "Both A and B",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answerSelectionType": "single",
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "At the highest level, React components have lifecycle events that fall into",
    "answers": [
      "Initialization",
      "Destruction",
      "State/Property Updates",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answerSelectionType": "single",
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method in a React Component should you override to stop the component from updating?",
    "answers": [
      "willComponentUpdate",
      "shouldComponentUpdate",
      "componentDidUpdate",
      "componentDidMount"
    ],
    "answerSelectionType": "single",
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What's used to pass data to a component from outside?",
    "answers": [
      "setState",
      "render with arguments",
      "PropTypes",
      "props"
    ],
    "answerSelectionType": "single",
    "correct": 3
  }
]